Document 1:

So thatÆs my plan. It will grow the economy and lower costs for families. 

So what are we waiting for? LetÆs get this done. And while youÆre at it, confirm my nominees to the Federal Reserve, which plays a critical role in fighting inflation.  

My plan will not only lower costs to give families a fair shot, it will lower the deficit.
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Document 2:

More infrastructure and innovation in America. 

More goods moving faster and cheaper in America. 

More jobs where you can earn a good living in America. 

And instead of relying on foreign supply chains, letÆs make it in America. 

Economists call it ôincreasing the productive capacity of our economy.ö 

I call it building a better America. 

My plan to fight inflation will lower your costs and lower the deficit.
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Document 3:

My plan to fight inflation will lower your costs and lower the deficit. 

17 Nobel laureates in economics say my plan will ease long-term inflationary pressures. Top business leaders and most Americans support my plan. And hereÆs the plan: 

First û cut the cost of prescription drugs. Just look at insulin. One in ten Americans has diabetes. In Virginia, I met a 13-year-old boy named Joshua Davis.
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Document 4:

But that trickle-down theory led to weaker economic growth, lower wages, bigger deficits, and the widest gap between those at the top and everyone else in nearly a century. 

Vice President Harris and I ran for office with a new economic vision for America. 

Invest in America. Educate Americans. Grow the workforce. Build the economy from the bottom up  
and the middle out, not from the top down.
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Document 5:

Our economy grew at a rate of 5.7% last year, the strongest growth in nearly 40 years, the first step in bringing fundamental change to an economy that hasnÆt worked for the working people of this nation for too long.  

For the past 40 years we were told that if we gave tax breaks to those at the very top, the benefits would trickle down to everyone else.
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Document 6:

Look at cars. 

Last year, there werenÆt enough semiconductors to make all the cars that people wanted to buy. 

And guess what, prices of automobiles went up. 

Soùwe have a choice. 

One way to fight inflation is to drive down wages and make Americans poorer.  

I have a better plan to fight inflation. 

Lower your costs, not your wages. 

Make more cars and semiconductors in America. 

More infrastructure and innovation in America. 

More goods moving faster and cheaper in America.
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Document 7:

My plan will not only lower costs to give families a fair shot, it will lower the deficit. 

The previous Administration not only ballooned the deficit with tax cuts for the very wealthy and corporations, it undermined the watchdogs whose job was to keep pandemic relief funds from being wasted. 

But in my administration, the watchdogs have been welcomed back. 

WeÆre going after the criminals who stole billions in relief money meant for small businesses and millions of Americans.
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Document 8:

I get it. ThatÆs why my top priority is getting prices under control. 

Look, our economy roared back faster than most predicted, but the pandemic meant that businesses had a hard time hiring enough workers to keep up production in their factories. 

The pandemic also disrupted global supply chains. 

When factories close, it takes longer to make goods and get them from the warehouse to the store, and prices go up. 

Look at cars.
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Document 9:

When we invest in our workers, when we build the economy from the bottom up and the middle out together, we can do something we havenÆt done in a long time: build a better America. 

For more than two years, COVID-19 has impacted every decision in our lives and the life of the nation. 

And I know youÆre tired, frustrated, and exhausted. 

But I also know this.
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Document 10:

My plan doesnÆt stop there. It also includes home and long-term care. More affordable housing. And Pre-K for every 3- and 4-year-old.  

All of these will lower costs. 

And under my plan, nobody earning less than $400,000 a year will pay an additional penny in new taxes. Nobody.  

The one thing all Americans agree on is that the tax system is not fair. We have to fix it.
