Document 1:

So thatÆs my plan. It will grow the economy and lower costs for families. 

So what are we waiting for? LetÆs get this done. And while youÆre at it, confirm my nominees to the Federal Reserve, which plays a critical role in fighting inflation.  

My plan will not only lower costs to give families a fair shot, it will lower the deficit.
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Document 2:

More infrastructure and innovation in America. 

More goods moving faster and cheaper in America. 

More jobs where you can earn a good living in America. 

And instead of relying on foreign supply chains, letÆs make it in America. 

Economists call it ôincreasing the productive capacity of our economy.ö 

I call it building a better America. 

My plan to fight inflation will lower your costs and lower the deficit.
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Document 3:

My plan to fight inflation will lower your costs and lower the deficit. 

17 Nobel laureates in economics say my plan will ease long-term inflationary pressures. Top business leaders and most Americans support my plan. And hereÆs the plan: 

First û cut the cost of prescription drugs. Just look at insulin. One in ten Americans has diabetes. In Virginia, I met a 13-year-old boy named Joshua Davis.
